There is a big good news for all the VLC brothers,
it has been brought out, now all the
CSC audio people, now VLC operators,
everyone will get salary, you people will
think how will they get it, how can they get it,
all the CSC operators in Bihar or India,
ABC operators,
when it is going to be private,
from where will they get the money, who will give the money, as I am going to
tell you in this video,
friends, you must be aware
that there are many government schemes
and this time such a big scheme has been brought out, you
see, I
also have a CSC ID, we are also
VLC operators, we
can do many works of this government, one has to work a
little hard to get it
and whoever gets this ID, it is great, after a lot of
hard work,
it is like we have on, so let's talk,
what is the offer, after all, if we tell you, then
you must know that the
number one bank is HDFC Bank, now whoever has an
HDFC Bank account,  CSC
operators are all shopkeepers who have
this ID, they can open an account from home.
You must be aware
that the largest branch is
HDFC Bank, in which thousands of
accounts are opened daily. You will get a good commission on one account. The
bigger the bank, the less the commission the
operator will earn. That is, you will get the
same commission as the bank gets.
After that, you will
also be given a salary of ₹5,6000.
After that, all the operators will also get a commission.
Along with this, the government is going to launch a scheme,
whose name is 'Aadhar Card'. Now you
can make anyone's Aadhar card and can also make corrections.
So, many schemes are going to come
and this type of scheme of HDFC has been
completed. It is very useful in that we can
open any person's account from here,
provide ATM card, take loan, if there is any
problem with it, then all the
people can fix it. There is no
need to go to the branch.
No one has this big good news, many
people are relieved of their questions, I wish I
also had a bank like this,
current account, big accounts,
RDA account is fixed, whatever number of
accounts you go to open in the branch,
all those accounts will be provided to you by a CSC operator at
your village, city, right there, it is done
friend, and from where will you
open the account, you see my
CSC ID is open on the display and it is going to be
updated very soon, as soon as it is updated, from
here, customers like you will get all
kinds of facilities that are provided in the bank,
you will get the same facility
in the shop, whatever facilities are provided to you in the bank, you can use the same
because you must be aware that
when the government has done a survey, it has been found that
all the VLC operators do
not make even the slightest mistake, they
help the government a lot by doing more or less than the bank or the manager,
hence the government has taken such a big decision
that all  All my operators who are in Bihar and
in India will be
given the work of opening a Khada, so friend, the
fruits of hard work are very sweet for them,
this ID is for everyone who applied two years ago and the
benefits of it are going to be received
now, friend, the story is because of
my hard work, so now sir,
its plan has been passed, now the story is,
we will also get salary every month between
one to five, we will also get
salary, plus we will
get commission, it will be fun to work,
you all will get money and if you work for the bank also, you will get
money, story is, now all of us
CSC operators can
get the post of manager like you, that's why
friends say that
voice has a lot of power of its own and cyber
cafes have a lot of power of its own
and the government also knows that whatever
economy is running today, there is a
study of cyber cafes that the people of cyber cafes are doing
any work very well
and reaching the government, that is why the
government has come up with such a big plan
that all the cyber cafes in Bihar
or  In India, for everyone, like HDFC mini
branch is being made, even today
you are seeing my shop, this is
correct, after a month HDFC mini branch will be made
automatic by the government, that is, HDFC bank
company people will come and make such shops for everyone,
now it will be less and the bank will also be less, the
facility which is provided in the bank, sir,
you will get the facility in the cyber cafe shop, you
can provide full service to the customer, from here you can apply for loan to the customer, can
provide loan to the customer, can deposit and withdraw customer's money,
can open an account, can
provide HDFC Bank ATM card,
many such home loan,
loan, whatever the loan is, all
can be provided from here,
in return you will get salary and you will
also get commission, every month you will get money between one and five,
money will be deposited in your account,
after that I will tell you that
very soon more such updates are going to happen
that all the VLC brothers, CLC
operators, all of them, like Aadhar card
update, it is also less,  It is going to happen, so
friends, I hope that you guys are going to get
good news very soon.
As far as I was aware,
I have told you this 100%, it is
not fake news. I am telling you the truth that
HDFC Bank, CSC IDF has got it done
very soon, it will just be
launched on the portal and it will start working as usual
and all the cyber cafes that are there will automatically
convert them into HDFC Bank mini branches, after that, just
like our lives will
change completely, so story no story
friend, always work hard, work diligently, the one who gives the fruits is the one who will give the fruits,
now whatever
hard work you will do, we had worked hard for it
two years ago, that is why we are going to get the fruits, so
you guys too, if any brother
wants to open a cyber cafe shop, then you guys should open it
properly or do not take tension and every
brother will gradually apply for his
CSC ID Operator
exam, pass it
and get a card made, story no story,
you will not get a government job but
Yes, you
can become a small branch manager through the bank, so this is
not a story, it is more for you people,
it will increase your value in the village, you will
also get respect friends, I hope
if you liked the information, then you will
definitely subscribe to
see more such videos, so we will
meet in the next video, till then
Jai Hind Jai Bharat, stay happy.